<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>com.skype.Client.desktop</id>
  <name>Skype</name>
  <developer_name>Microsoft</developer_name>
  <summary>Call and message skype users, with video chat support</summary>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>LicenseRef-proprietary</project_license>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.skype.com</url>
  <description>
    <p>Skype makes staying in touch incredibly easy and fun!
    If you have a webcam and a microphone, you can easily make video calls and voice calls to anyone in the world who also has Skype.
    This app’s features are simple to use and you can stay in touch with people anywhere in world!</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot>
      <image type="source">https://secure.skypeassets.com/content/dam/scom/download/skype-for-linux.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <categories>
    <category>Application</category>
    <category>Network</category>
  </categories>
  <!-- These are the icons for the android apps, from https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.skype.raider -->
  <icon type="remote" height="64" width="64">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/QfAEt_ya6-n8w_TD9-PsghFC2DMSO7fLGNZB4cQ3RtbBbHFkXJE_gxOc3l32-j6LXg=w64</icon>
  <icon type="remote" height="128" width="128">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/QfAEt_ya6-n8w_TD9-PsghFC2DMSO7fLGNZB4cQ3RtbBbHFkXJE_gxOc3l32-j6LXg=w128</icon>
  <releases>
    <release date="2019-04-30" version="8.44.0.40">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Improvements to message forwarding: You can now forward a quoted message. </li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2018-11-12" version="8.34.0.78">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Switch between cameras: Easily switch between multiple cameras during a video call, just right-click or long press on your avatar to select a different camera.</li>
          <li>Easily share Skype contact details with others: From a chat, select the share contact contact card button button, select a contact to share, and then select send.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2018-10-20" version="8.33.0.41">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Send message with Enter key: Change what your Enter key does while in a chat, set it to send the message or insert a new line. Go to your profile picture > Settings > Messaging.</li>
          <li>Add a phone number as a contact: Easily add someone's phone number as a contact in Skype.</li>
          <li>Mute and remove participants during a Skype group call: When you initiate a group call, you can mute or remove participants during the call.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2018-08-29" version="8.29.0.50">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li> Signed in as: Have multiple Skype or Microsoft accounts? Tap your profile picture and both your Skype Name and the account you're signed in as will be displayed.</li>
          <li>Archive your conversations: Hide your conversations by archiving them.</li>
          <li> Stop unwanted calls: Now, you can avoid those distractions and choose to only allow calls from your contacts to ring. </li>
          <li> Cortana is now available in the United Kingdom </li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2018-08-14" version="8.28.0.41">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li> Record your calls: Introducing cloud-based Skype call recording directly from the app.</li>
          <li> Color filters for photos: Use color filters to inject some charm into new or existing photos and delight your friends! </li>
          <li> Spotify: Music lovers can now search for songs, albums and artists, preview, play, and share music on Spotify! Just select the Add to chat button to get started. </li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2018-08-03" version="8.27.0.85"/>
  </releases>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
    <content_attribute id="social-chat">intense</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-info">moderate</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-audio">intense</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-contacts">intense</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-purchasing">intense</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
</component>
